back in the mid90s Microsoft wanted
Windows 95 in every home that's why they
hired friend Stars Matthew Perry and
Jennifer Anderson to teach people about
the sexy Fun World of the PC operating
system and could it be any more
hilarious okay now let's load up the
task bar I'll show you what it does task
bar is that anything like a Snickers bar
does that have nougat what is nougat
does anybody know
that oh
Jesus this lady's like God damn it I
knew we should have gotten Frasier why
do we do this oh my God ah it's not
their fault comedian friends up I mean
you know they did this corporate gig
they probably got paid a ton of money
they like well no one's ever going to
see this this looks like it's 50 years
ago like Jennifer Anderson looks like a
Puerto Rican bank teller bad at Ma like
what is she looks so different now I
know she used to eat I know comedians
Friends episodes were always titled
things like the one where Joey moves out
or the one with the chickenpox what is
this episode episode called Jamie uh the
one where Rachel dates a Nigerian prince
yeah points just to help him transfer
the money yeah uh Michelle um this is
the one actually where she finds out
that John void's daughter is going to
steal her man
later CL your legs to married men
and all know that worked out
great